今天你说了，你说了又说，但我认为你警告了世界，你将参加下一届世界杯。
Today you said it, you said it without saying it, but I think you warned the world that you are going to be in the next World Cup.
Hoy lo dijiste, lo dijiste sin decirlo, pero creo que le avisaste al mundo que vas a estar en el mundial que viene.
我没有向你要求任何东西，我只是认为这就是说，嘿，看我很好。
I'm not asking you for anything, I just think it was a definition of saying, hey, look I'm fine.
No te pido nada, solamente creo que fue una definición de decir, che, miren que estoy bien.
一如既往，我已经重复了一遍，我也告诉过你了。
As always, I already repeated it, I told you too.
Como siempre, ya lo repetí, te lo dije a vos también.
很享受，今天我真的很喜欢一切的结果，我想再玩一次。
Enjoying, today I really enjoyed how everything turned out, I wanted to play again.
disfrutando, hoy lo disfruté muchísimo como se dio todo, tenía ganas de volver a jugar.
在我想再次为国家队效力的国家，我在那里呆了很长时间
In the country I wanted to play with the national team again, I was there for a long time
en el país tenía ganas de volver a jugar con la selección estuve mucho tiempo
站着享受这些时刻，今天我很享受
standing and enjoying these moments, today I enjoy it
parado y bueno disfrutar de estos momentos, hoy lo disfruto
人们的呼声比以往任何时候都更加强烈，他们如何对待我。
more than ever the cry of the people, how they treat me.
más que nunca el grito de la gente, cómo nos trata a mí.
对于整个团队来说，这种联系已经存在很长时间了。
to the entire team, the connection that has existed for a long time.
a todo el equipo, la conexión que hay desde hace ya mucho tiempo.
我们能够再次获胜，踢得很好，每个人都很高兴。
We were able to win again, play well and everyone was happy.
pudimos volver a ganar, a jugar bien y todo contento.
你在送给朱利安的卡片上的小脸，我的意思是，你从第一天起就会享受它，这家伙确实......
The little face that you put on the card that you give to Julián, I mean, you're going to enjoy it from the first day, the guy does...
La carita que pusiste en la hocha que le pones a Julián, digo, se te va a disfrutar desde el primer día, el tipo hace...
20年前的相同目标并享受它，就好像它是一个请求一样。
the same goals 20 years ago and enjoy it as if it were a request.
los mismos goles hace 20 años y disfruta como si fuese un pide.
是的，我真的很喜欢呆在这里，我已经说过了。
Yes, I really enjoy being here, I already said it.
Sí, disfruto mucho la verdad de estar acá, lo dije ya.
我每天在小组里过得很开心。
I have a good time within the group, on a day-to-day basis.
La paso bien dentro del grupo, en el día a día.
我喜欢呆在现场，喜欢和我的伴侣在一起。
I like being on the premises, I like being with my partner.
Me gusta estar en el predio, me gusta estar con mi compañero.
我喜欢这个领域，因为今天我们的人......
I enjoy the field because today we have people who...
Disfruto dentro de la cancha porque hoy tenemos gente que...
谁打得很好，谁总是想建议打球，我们不明白。
who plays very well and who always wants to suggest playing, we don't understand.
que juega muy bien y que quiere siempre proponer jugar, no entendemos.
我认为人们也喜欢它，这是我们能做的非常好的事情。
and I think people also enjoy it and that is very nice what we can do.
y creo que la gente también disfruta y eso es muy lindo lo que podemos llegar a hacer.
因为人们付出了巨大的努力来观看它。
because people make a great effort to come see it.
porque la gente hace un esfuerzo muy grande para venir a verla.
球队虽然每次比赛总是爆满，但这就是他们付出的努力。
The team, although it is always full every time we play, that is the effort it makes.
La selección, si bien siempre está llena cada vez que jugamos, ese es el esfuerzo que hace.
能够提供这一点并让他们满意地离开并享受他们所看到的一切并不容易。
It is not easy to be able to provide this and have them leave happy and enjoy what they see.
No es fácil poder brindarle esto y que se vayan felices y disfruten de lo que ven.
这也是一个额外的奖励。
It is also an extra prize.
también es un premio extra.
你拍的照片，因为有一张照片正在对你做这个，在球门前做出拥抱的手势。
The photo that you took, because there is a photo that is doing this to you, making a gesture of the hug at the goal.
La foto que te llevaste, porque hay una foto que te está haciendo así, haciendo gesto a vos del abrazo en el gol.
朱利安说，不，我拍的照片是我们三个人庆祝的。
And Julián said, no, and the photo that I took is the three of us celebrating.
Y Julián decía, no, y la foto que me llevo yo, somos los tres festejando.
这也是你所创造的，最伟大的东西。
That is what you also generated, the greatest thing.
Eso es lo que generaron también ustedes, lo más grande.
和孩子们在一起，他们安定下来并给了他们一切。
with the kids, who settled down and who give them everything.
con los más pibes, que se asentaron y que les dan de todo.
嗯，多年来一直如此，事实是，有一个非常好的团队，正如我刚才所说，我们很享受。
Well, it's been like this for years now, the truth is that there is a very nice group, as I said just now, we enjoy it.
Bueno, ya hace años que viene siendo así, la verdad que hay un grupo muy lindo, como decía recién, disfrutamos de él.
在一起的小细节。
of being together, of the small details.
de estar juntos, de los pequeños detalles.
我们不介意集中精力，把时间关在家里，因为我们玩得很开心……
It doesn't bother us to concentrate and spend time locked up because we have a great time...
No nos molesta concentrar y estar tiempo encerrado porque la pasamos...
我们玩得很开心，没什么，今天我们很幸运。
We had a good time and, nothing, today we were lucky.
La pasamos bien y, nada, hoy tuvimos la suerte.
另一个像尼科这样的小男孩，他有一个广阔的未来，他有很​​多品质，他适应得很快。
Another young boy like Nico who has a huge future, who has a lot of quality, who adapts very quickly.
Otro chico joven como Nico que tiene un futuro enorme, que tiene mucha calidad, que se adapta rapidísimo.
给团队，希望我们能做到
to the group and hopefully we on our side can do it
al grupo y ojalá nosotros en nuestro lado lo podamos
也帮助他继续成长，为了自己的利益，为了团队的利益，为了……
Also help him continue growing for his own good, for the good of the team and for...
ayudar también a seguir creciendo para el bien de él, para el bien de la selección y para...
继续使这个团体变得强大。
to continue making this group strong.
para seguir haciendo fuerte a este grupo.
或国家队T恤。
or the national team t-shirt.
o la camiseta de la selección.
换句话说，我们正在谈论奴隶制。
In other words, we are talking about slavery.
O sea, estamos hablando de una esclavura.
那个球在哪里？
Where is that ball?
¿Dónde está esa pelota?
你拿了吗？
Did you take it?
¿Te la llevaste?
不，他们只是告诉我的。
No, they just told me that.
No, me dijeron justo recién eso.
马里托有，下次他会帮我保存的。
Marito has it, he'll save it for me next time.
La tiene Marito, me la guarda la próxima.
还是为了博物馆？
Or for the museum?
¿O para el museo?
是的，显然。
Yes, obviously.
Sí, obviamente.
事实上，我想我这里保存了一对。
In fact, I think I have a couple saved here.
Es más, creo que tengo un par acá guardado.
我看到许多逆境，作为一个团队，他们总能克服它们。
I see many adversities and as a group they can always overcome them.
Yo veo muchas adversidades y también como grupo las pueden superar siempre.
是的，委内瑞拉的比赛很困难，因为我们必须经历的一切，因为旅行，事实是......
Yes, the Venezuela game was difficult because of everything we had to experience, because of the trip, the truth is...
Sí, fue difícil el partido de Venezuela por todo lo que tuvimos que vivir, por el viaje, la verdad que...
代表团曾考虑前往迈阿密以使一切变得更容易。
that the delegation had thought about going to Miami to make everything easier.
que la delegación había pensado ir a Miami para que sea todo más fácil.
由于旅行、回程、大量费用和长途旅行，最终使一切变得复杂。
and it ended up complicating everything due to the trips, the return too, a lot of expense and long trips.
y terminó complicando todo por los viajes, la vuelta también, mucho de gasto y viajes largos.
我们的法庭演奏并提出我们一直在做的事情，我们所做的事情
our court to play and propose what we always do, what we did
la cancha nuestra para jugar y proponer lo que nosotros hacemos siempre, lo que hicimos
但是，嘿，那天我们知道如何让他退出比赛。
But hey, we knew how to get him out of the game that day.
Pero bueno, lo supimos sacar del partido ese día.
另一方面，今天我们必须赢。
on the other hand and today we had to win.
de otro lado y hoy teníamos que ganar.
继续做好这一切并继续成长...
to continue doing all that well and continue growing as...
para seguir haciendo bueno todo eso y seguir creciendo nosotros como...
作为一个团体，超越这一事实，距离再迈出一步还有很长的路要走
as a group and beyond the fact that there is a long distance to take one more step towards
como grupo y más allá de que hay una distancia grande de dar un pasito más para
尽快获得资格。
to qualify as soon as possible.
para clasificarnos lo antes posible.
你怎么了？
What's up with you?
¿Qué onda le metiste?
是不是很运动呢？
Isn't it sporty?
¿No es deportivo?
不，不，在上面加一点半外套。
No, no, put a little half coat on top.
No, no, pon un poco de media capa arriba.
没什么，好吧，我去...
Nothing, well, I'm going to...
Nada, bueno, me voy a...
我要离开了，我要去旅行，好吧，我也见过自己有点像那样。
I'm leaving and I have to travel, so well, I've seen myself a little like that.
me voy y me tengo que viajar, así que bueno, yo me he visto un poco así.
作为？
As?
¿Cómo?
没有 2x1 且带有 10 的袋子。
The bag without a 2x1 with the 10.
El bolsito sin un 2x1 con el 10.
不，最重要的是我想要罗莎和矮人，好吧，他们已经到处出现了，所以我告诉他，你搞砸了，我不知道是什么。
No, on top of that I wanted the Rosa and the dwarf, well, they were already appearing everywhere so I told him, you screwed up, I don't know what.
No, encima yo quería el Rosa y el enano, bueno, ya salían todos lados así que le dije, me lo cagaste, no sé qué.
但是，嘿，对他来说，把它交给他要容易一些。
But hey, it's a little easier for him to get it to him.
Pero bueno, él tiene un poco más de facilidad para que le llegue.
听着，用一个词来形容他今天打的比赛。
Listen, one word describes the game he played today.
Escuchá, me describen una palabra el partido que hizo hoy.
我只是告诉劳塔罗，他告诉我们他会参加下一届世界杯，但没有在这里告诉我们，因为我认为如果不……
I was just telling Lautaro that he told us without telling us here that he is going to be in the next World Cup because I think that if not...
Yo le decía recién a Lautaro que nos dijo sin decirnos acá que va a estar en el mundial que viene porque creo que si no...
如果他没有出现在那里，他们就会在迈阿密的房子里寻找他。
If he doesn't appear there, they will look for him in Miami, at the house.
si no aparece ahí, le van a buscar a Miami, a la casa.
我们很享受它，但现实是......
We enjoyed it a lot, the reality is that...
Nosotros lo disfrutamos un montón, la realidad es que...
他们一直在问我们，也一直在问他关于下一届世界杯的事情。
They keep asking us and they keep asking him about the next World Cup.
Nos siguen preguntando y le siguen preguntando a él sobre la próxima Copa del Mundo.
这是一个现实，因为我知道，而他不知道。
And it is a reality, because I know it, that he does not know it.
Y es una realidad, porque lo sé yo, que él no lo sabe.
他活在当下，岁月流逝一切。
He lives in the present, the years pass for everything.
Él vive el presente, los años pasan para todo.
我们每天都很享受，但今天显然已经证明了这一点
We really enjoy it every day, but today obviously has shown that
Nosotros lo super disfrutamos todos los días, pero bueno hoy obviamente que ha demostrado que
他仍然是最好的，我希望他能感觉到
He is still the best of all and I hope he feels
sigue siendo el mejor de todos y ojalá se sienta
最重要的是，带着渴望，因为他知道我们非常渴望继续依靠他。
With desire, above all, because he knows that we are dying to continue counting on him.
Con ganas, sobre todo, porque sabe que nosotros nos morimos por seguir contando con él.
如果没有，就让他作为有史以来最好的球员离开吧。
and if not, let him leave as the best of all time.
y si no es así, que se vaya como lo que es el mejor de todos los tiempos.
对于所有谈论过在巴兰基亚、在马图林发生的事情的人来说，这里是世界冠军球队，这里是……
For all those who had talked about what had happened in Barranquilla, in Maturín, here is the world champion team, here is...
Para todos aquellos que habían hablado de lo que había pasado en Barranquilla, en Maturín, acá está la selección campeona del mundo, acá está...
斯卡罗尼时代最好的、最好的比赛之一？
The best, one of the best games of the Scaloni Era?
¿El mejor, uno de los mejores partidos de la Era Scaloni?
不。
No.
我们将继续成为世界冠军，直到下一届世界杯，我们将继续成为美国队的两届冠军。
We continue to be the world champions until the next World Cup, we will continue to be the two-time champion of America.
Seguimos siendo los campeones del mundo hasta el próximo Mundial, seguiremos siendo el bicampeón de América.
不，我不认为我们总是为人民而踢球，给人们带来欢乐，继续下去
No, I don't think that we always play for the people, to give people joy, to continue
No, no creo que nosotros siempre jugamos para la gente, para darle alegría a la gente, para seguir
代表团队与...
representing the team with...
representando a la selección con...
我们的价值观和强度。
with the values ​​and with the intensity with which we do it.
con los valores y con la intensidad en la que lo hacemos.
显然，球队不比赛，不学习，一切都充满活力。
Obviously the teams don't play, they don't study and everything is very dynamic.
Obviamente que los equipos no juegan, no se estudian y todo es muy dinámico.
但没什么，我认为我们今天踢了一场精彩的比赛，仅此而已。
But nothing, I think we played a good game today and that's it.
Pero nada, creo que hoy hicimos un buen partido y ya.
罗德里，你参与这次评选感觉如何？
Rodri, how do you feel being part of this selection?
Rodri, ¿cómo te sentís siendo parte de esta selección?
当谈到足球时，我想做得有点过分，但最重要的是外面发生的事情是一个给人们带来很多欢乐的人类团体。
I want to go a little overboard when it comes to football, but above all what happens outside is a human group that brings a lot of joy to people.
Me quiero exceder un poco en lo futbolístico, pero que sobre todo lo que se da afuera es un grupo humano y que le da muchas alegrías a la gente.
超级自豪，真的。
Super proud, really.
Super orgulloso, la verdad.
这让我非常自豪属于
It makes me very proud to belong to
Me da mucho orgullo pertenecer a
对于这个团队，对于它所取得的一切，尤其是在方式上。
to this team, to everything it achieved, especially in the way.
a este equipo, a todo lo que consiguió, sobre todo de la manera.
一路走来，他们取得了很多成就，而不仅仅是头衔。
along the way, many things they achieve, not just the titles.
del camino, muchas cosas que consiguen, no solo los títulos.
最重要的是，他给这个国家带来了希望，给了这个国家很多幸福。
and above all he restored hope to a country, he gave it a lot of happiness.
y sobre todo le devolvió la ilusión a un país, le dio mucha felicidad.
这是买不来的，事实是生活中有些东西
and that cannot be bought, the truth is there are things that in life
y eso no se puede comprar, la verdad hay cosas que en la vida
他们不会给你任何东西，而且我们是一个非常小的团体。
They don't give you anything and we are a very small group.
no te la dan nada y nosotros somos un grupo muy pequeño.
谁正在实现它，就会继续这样做，对我来说，属于其中是完全的自豪。
who is achieving it, continues to do it and for me to belong to that is total pride.
que lo está logrando, lo sigue haciendo y para mí pertenecer a eso es orgullo total.
你也看到哪面旗帜了吗？
Did you see which flag too?
¿Viste qué bandera también?
你看到那面旗帜了，对吧？
You saw that flag there, right?
¿Viste qué bandera allá, no?
你见过吗？
Have you seen it?
¿La viste?
不，你在哥伦比亚、委内瑞拉、这里也看到过。
No, you saw it in Colombia, in Venezuela, here too.
No, la viste en Colombia, en Venezuela, acá también.
尊重队伍，特拉普无处不在。
Respect the ranks, Trapu who goes everywhere.
Respeten los rangos, Trapu que va a todos lados.
就是这样？
That's it?
¿Ya está?
它留下来了吗？
Did it stay?
¿Quedó?
我没看到，我没看到。
I didn't see it, I didn't see it.
No la vi, no la vi.
我们做了之前的事情，一切。
We did the previous thing, everything.
Hicimos tal la previa, todo.
不，事实是……
No, and the truth is...
No, y la verdad que...
那里流传着一句话，我来自二号队，我看起来有点热，因为我不能和孩子们一起庆祝。
It was a phrase that came out there, that I came from the 2nd, I looked half hot because I couldn't be celebrating with the boys.
Fue una frase que salió ahí, que yo venía del 2, pintaba medio caliente porque no podía estar festejando con los muchachos.
我不知道，它出来了，人们喜欢它，好吧，它坚持了下来，很好。
And I don't know, it came out and people liked it and well, it stuck and it's fine.
Y no sé, me salió y la gente le gustó y bueno, sí quedó y está bien.
你必须在抹布上签名。
You're going to have to sign the rag.
Vas a tener que firmar el trapo.
是的，我想要它，事实是我想要它。
Yes, I would like it, the truth is that I would like it.
Sí, me gustaría, la verdad que me gustaría.
历史上的阿根廷，78、86和22标志。
The Argentina of history, 78, 86 and 22 logos.
La Argentina de la historia, 78, 86 y 22 logos.
……之后你现在说什么？
What do you say now after...?
¿Qué decís ahora después...?
我没说什么，大家都很好。
I'm not saying anything, everyone was very good.
No digo nada, todos fueron muy bien.
尊重花束。
Respect the bouquets.
Respeten los ramos.
我请你用一个词来定义你的队长 10 号今天的比赛。
I ask you to define in one word the game of your captain, the 10, today.
Te pido que me definas en una palabra el partido hoy de su capitán, del 10.
仔细想想，那就启航了，我们现在是儿童保护时间，我们已经过了，我们不在。
Think carefully, then it will set sail, we are in child protection hours, we have already passed it, we are not there.
Pensá bien, después zarpara, estamos en horario de protección al menor, ya lo pasamos, no estamos.
没有衣服。
Without clothes.
Sin ropa.
不穿衣服是吗？
Without clothes, right?
Sin ropa, ¿no?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
裸！
Naked!
¡Desnudo!
玩的时候就裸体了！
Naked did it when you played!
¡Desnudo lo hizo cuando jugaste!
是的，这确实令人印象深刻。
Yes, it's really impressive.
Sí, la verdad que impresionante.
一个事实是...
A truth was...
Una verdad era...
疯狂，对扎赫勒的钦佩，对扎赫勒的感激
madness, admiration for Zahel, gratitude for
locura, admiración a Zahel, agradecimiento por
他为我们所有人树立了榜样，让我们​​继续竞争，继续追求更多，这对年轻人有好处。
for the example he gives to all of us to continue competing, to continue wanting more and that is good for young people.
por el ejemplo que nos da a todos nosotros de seguir compitiendo, de seguir queriendo más y eso a los jóvenes nos hace bien.
你抓住他，把他绑起来，这就是发生在你身上的事。
You grabbed him, you tied him, that's what happened to you.
Lo agarraste, lo amarraste, es la que te pasó.
是的，因为好吧，这周......
Yes, because well, the week...
Sí, porque bueno, la semana...
我们一直在练习一些没有成功的戏剧，没有成功，幸运的是......
We had been practicing a couple of plays that didn't work out, that didn't work out and well, luckily...
Veníamos practicando un par de jugadas que no salían, que no salían y bueno, por suerte...
在压力下，他能够将篮板球传给他，然后……
in a pressure he was able to after give the rebound to him and after the...
en una presión pudo después que darle el rebote a él y después de la...
我能够在禁区内将球传回给自己，并且能够进球，所以没什么，很高兴。
I was able to return it to myself there in the area and I was able to score the goal, so nothing, happy.
Me la pude devolver ahí en el área y pude hacer el gol, así que nada, contento.
你永远不会感到疲倦，我的意思是，动力来自它所来的地方。
You never get tired, I mean, the motivation comes from where it comes.
No se cansan nunca ustedes, digo, la motivación de dónde sale.
是的，嗯，我想已经能够成为这件衬衫了。
Yes, well, I imagine that being able to be the shirt already is.
Sí, bien, me imagino que poder ser la camiseta ya lo es.
但可怕的是，比如在这个球场上，他们并没有失去任何东西。
but it's terrible, on this court, for example, they didn't lose anything.
pero es terrible, en esta cancha, por ejemplo, no perdieron nada.
他们甚至从未取得过进球，从家乡来到这里，现在又回到这里踢球，但是是什么一直激励着他们呢？
that they never even scored a goal, coming here from their home, now they come back to play here, but what motivates them all the time?
que nunca ni siquiera les metieron un gol, venir acá ya de su casa, ahora vuelven a jugar acá, pero ¿qué los moviliza todo el tiempo?
继续比赛，教练的信息，他的信息，正如我告诉你的。
Continue competing, the coach's message, his message, as I tell you.
Seguir compitiendo, el mensaje del entrenador, el mensaje de él, como te digo.
它促使我们继续竞争，继续想要更多。
It pushes us to continue competing, to continue wanting more.
Nos empuja a seguir compitiendo, a seguir queriendo más.
我们也对此习以为常。
We are also used to this.
Nosotros también estamos acostumbrados a esto.
我们也试图传达这一点。
We try to convey this as well.
Tratamos de transmitir esto también.
在我的俱乐部，这正是我想要的，继续与国米一起取得成就。
In my club, that is exactly what I want, to continue achieving things with Inter.
Yo en mi club puntualmente es lo que quiero, seguir consiguiendo cosas con el Inter.
每天都在提高等级，这就是这个游戏的意义所在。
every day raising the level and this is what this game is about.
todos los días alzando el nivel y de esto se trata este juego.
你知道你的每一个进球都离金球奖更近一步，因为人们也是这样要求的。
You know that every goal you score is one more step closer to the Ballon d'Or, because people ask for it that way too.
Sabes que cada gol que haces es un pasito más que estás cerca del balón de oro, porque la gente lo pide así también.
老实说，如果你赢了，那就太好了。
And it would be beautiful, honestly, if you win it.
Y sería hermoso, la verdad, que lo ganes.
事实是，是的，我将和我的妻子一起出席颁奖典礼。
The truth is, yes, I will be there with my wife at the award ceremony.
La verdad que sí, estaré ahí con mi mujer en la premiación.
带着一如既往的热情，我总是说
With the same enthusiasm as always, I always say that
Con la ilusión de siempre, siempre digo que
集体高于个人，但我认为去年
that the collective is above the individual, but I think that last year
que lo colectivo está por encima de lo individual, pero creo que el año pasado
在国际米兰度过了精彩的一年。
A spectacular year with Inter.
Un año espectacular con el Inter.
我用...完成了它
I finished it off with...
Lo terminé de redondear con...
并在美洲杯上打进 5 粒进球，夺得冠军。
with the title, with 5 goals in the Copa América.
con el título, con los 5 goles en la Copa América.
好吧，分析一切，我想我在那里......你不值得。
And well, analyzing everything, I think I'm there to be... You don't deserve it.
Y bueno, analizando todo, yo creo que estoy ahí para estar... No mereces.
是的，好吧，我不想这么说，但我...
Yeah, well, I don't want to say that, but I'm...
Sí, bueno, no quiero decir eso, pero estoy...
我很好，我很高兴，很兴奋，我们会看看那天晚上会发生什么。
I'm fine, I'm happy, excited and we'll see what happens that night.
Estoy bien, estoy contento, ilusionado y veremos qué pasa esa noche.
他们最终能够一起玩耍。
They were able to play together in the end.
pudieron jugar juntos al final.
朱利安、劳塔罗、梅西。
Julián, Lautaro, Messi.
第一次出发，但我认为这是一个信息，这场胜利是历史性的。
First time starting, but I think it was a message, this win is historic.
Primera vez de arranque, pero creo que era un mensaje, esta goleada es histórica.
是的，我们有时也会尝试适应
yes well we try to adapt sometimes too
si bueno tratamos de adaptarnos también a veces
正如教练所说，他重复了一遍，球队的平衡也很重要。
As the coach says, as he repeats, the balance of the team is also important.
como dice el entrenador, como lo repite, el equilibrio del equipo también es importante.
到时候我们会像今天一样尝试这样做。
When it's time we will try to do it like we did today.
Cuando toque trataremos de hacerlo como lo hicimos hoy.
也参与防守，因为这就是它的意义，被封闭，当......
giving a hand in defense too, because that's what it's about, being closed and when...
dando una mano en defensa también, porque de eso se trata, estar cerradito y cuando...
我们有进攻的机会，进攻三分也很重要。
We have the opportunity to attack, attacking three is also important.
Tenemos la oportunidad de atacar, atacar tres también es importante.
占据整个攻击前沿并根据其他队友的动作进行移动。
occupy the entire attack front and move depending on the movement made by the other teammate.
ocupar todo el frente de ataque y moverse dependiendo del movimiento que haga el otro compañero.
现在最后一个，今天他没有说他要参加2026年比赛，他要参加世界杯。
Now the last one, today he said it without saying that he is going to play in 2026, that he is going to play in the World Cup.
Ahora la última, hoy lo dijo sin decirlo que va a jugar el 2026, que va a jugar el mundial.
虽然没有用言语表达出来，但我想...
Without saying it in words, but I think...
Sin decirlo con palabras, pero creo que...
如果他不这样做，你就去迈阿密找他。
If he doesn't, you're going to look for him in Miami.
Si no lo hace, le van a buscar ustedes a Miami.
他不需要说什么，他必须来，穿上球衣，上场比赛。
He doesn't have to say anything, he has to come, put on the shirt, play.
Es que no tiene que decir nada, tiene que venir, ponerse la camiseta, jugar.
因为它是我们的象征、我们的队长和我们的榜样。
because it is our emblem, our captain and our example.
porque es nuestro emblema, nuestro capitán y nuestro ejemplo.
虽然他已经在这个弧线得分了。
Although he had already scored in this arc.
Si bien ya había marcado en este arco.
在这个球场上，第一个正式进球，我想......
and on this field, the first official goal, I imagine that...
y en esta cancha, el primer gol oficial, me imagino que...
感觉很好，除了他的光子，Leo 在那里大喊大叫，太壮观了，我已经看到那个上传​​到 Instagram 了，太壮观了。
that feels nice apart from his photon with Leo there shouting it, spectacular I already saw that one uploaded to Instagram, spectacular.
que se siente lindo aparte de su fotón con Leo ahí gritándolo, espectacular esa ya la vi subida a Instagram, espectacular.
是的，事实是我非常高兴，对于第一个正式进球感到非常高兴。
Yes, the truth is that I am very happy, very happy for this first official goal.
Sí, la verdad que muy contento, muy feliz por este primer gol oficial.
正如我刚才告诉你的，非常高兴。
As I just told you, very happy.
Como te dije recién muy contento.
这是一个伟大的进球，这很好，因为有一个很好的组合，它是由利奥发起的。
It was a great goal, it was nice because there was a good combination, it was started by Leo.
Fue un golazo, fue lindo porque hubo una buena combinación, la inició Leo.
你读了吗？
Did you read?
¿Leíste?
空气与什么？
Air with what?
¿De aire con qué?
是的，是的，我告诉莫莉，它是中辣的，我用小腿抓住了它，但是，幸运的是，它没有越过我的头，它进入了球门。
Yes, yes, I told Molly that it was medium spicy and that I grabbed it with my shin, but well, luckily it didn't go over my head, it went inside the goal.
Sí, sí, le dije a Molly que venía medio picante y que la agarré con la canilla, pero bueno, por suerte no se me fue arriba, fue adentro del arco.
那时是用水龙头吗？
Was it with the tap then?
¿Fue con la canilla entonces?
是的，是的，他打了我的小腿一点，听我说，那天我很生气。
Yes, yes, he hit me a little on the shin. Listen to me, I was angry the other day.
Sí, sí, me pegó un poquito en la canilla Escúchame, estaba con bronca por el otro día
在委内瑞拉开始比赛，场地根本没有帮助，你必须出去......
starting game in Venezuela, the field didn't help at all, you had to go out...
partido titular en Venezuela, la cancha no ayudaba nada, te tocó salir...
中场休息时你还有一个刺，今天你解决了它。
At halftime you still have a thorn, today you were able to resolve it.
en el entretiempo te queda una espinita, hoy justamente lo pudiste recontra saldar.
不，不，事实是我很高兴，我有机会作为首发出场。
No, no, the truth is that I was very happy, that I had had the opportunity to play as a starter.
No, no, la verdad que estaba muy contento, que me había tocado la oportunidad de jugar titular.
我的状态并不好，但我对每一个机会都很高兴，并努力充分利用它。
I was not in condition, but happy for every opportunity and trying to make the most of it.
No estaba en condiciones, pero contento por cada oportunidad y tratar de aprovecharla al máximo.
你告诉我的那一天，因为今天这不仅仅是对劳塔罗说的，用一个词来为我定义他今天踢的比赛。
The day you tell me, because today it wasn't just said to Lautaro, define for me in one word the game he played today.
El día que me decís, porque hoy no se recién le decía a Lautaro, definime en una palabra el partido que jugó hoy.
他告诉我，没有衣服。
Without clothes, he told me.
Sin ropa, me dijo.
你如何定义梅西今天打出的三粒进球和两次助攻的比赛？
How do you define the game that Messi played today with three goals and two assists?
¿Cómo defines el partido que jugó Messi hoy con tres goles y dos asistencias?
是的，他看起来很像刚出道的狮子座。
Yes, he looks like the Leo who just debuted.
Sí, parece el Leo que recién debutó.
一切都变得越来越好，我们已经没有什么了......
It's getting better and better and there's nothing for us...
cada vez está mejor y nada nosotros...
我们在球场上、室外都很享受，为他和我们所有人感到非常高兴。
We enjoyed it on the field, outside, so very happy for him and for all of us.
lo disfrutamos dentro de la cancha, afuera, así que muy contento por él y por todos nosotros.
好吧，我想你很快就会想回到这个领域，特别是因为那里有解放者杯决赛。
Well, I imagine that you are going to want to return to this field soon, especially because of the Libertadores finals, which are there.
Bueno, imagino que vas a tener ganas de volver pronto a esta cancha, sobre todo por los finales de Libertadores, que están ahí.
我们有佩纳罗尔，一个讨厌的对手。
We have Peñarol, a screwed rival.
Nos toca Peñarol, un rival jodido.
但是，嘿，现在我们周五比赛，然后我们将为周三的比赛做准备，我们必须……
But hey, now we play on Friday and then we'll prepare for Wednesday's game, which we have to...
Pero bueno, ahora jugamos el viernes y después a preparar el partido del miércoles que tenemos que...
来这里玩，希望上帝愿意。
to come and play here, hopefully God willing.
que venir a jugar acá ojalá Dios quiera.
周五，你的前球队贝莱斯·阿尔菲尔 (Vélez Arfil) 将与你的球队比赛，他坚持与球队一起度过了美好的五年。
On Friday your former team Vélez Arfil plays, with whom he insists for a good five years.
El viernes juega tu ex-equipo Vélez Arfil, con quien insiste un buen acaso de cinco años.
你看清楚了，在更衣室里怨恨总统，我不知道你有没有说话。
You see it well, resent the president here in the locker room, I don't know if you spoke.
Lo ves bien, resenta al presidente acá en el vestuario, no sé si hablaste.
是的，是的，我看到了他，我在那里看到了主席，我把球衣给了他，我对他很有感情，他很小的时候就认识我了。
Yes, yes, I saw him, I saw the president there, I gave him the shirt, I have great affection for him, he knows me very young.
Sí, sí, lo vi, lo vi al presidente ahí, le di la camiseta, le tengo un gran cariño, él me conoce muy chico.
但他确实告诉我他们在这里比赛，我祝他一切顺利。
But he did tell me that they played here and well I wish him the best.
pero sí me dijo que jugaban acá y bueno le deseo lo mejor.
您认为球队表现如何？
How do you see the team doing well?
¿Cómo lo ves bien, al equipo?
是的，是的，我关注比赛，我认为他们非常好，他们必须继续这样。
Yes, yes, I follow the games, I think they are very good and they have to continue like this.
Sí, sí, sigo los partidos, creo que están muy bien y tienen que seguir así.